cbgraph.com 2010-12-30

# Privacy Policy | CBGraph

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect**

General Information: If you subscribe for, purchase or otherwise make use of our products and services, we may collect personal information from you, including your name, age, address, e-mail address and facts about your computers, profession and similar information. We do not, however, knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

Web Site Usage Information: We automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information from you when you visit our Web site. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors and members use and navigate our Web sites on an aggregate basis, including the number and frequency of visitors and subscribers to each Web page, and the length of their visits.

**The Way We Use Information**

We may use information in the following ways:

  * To send you e-mail notifications about our new or existing products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you.
  * To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services, or other internal business purposes.
  * To provide third parties with _aggregate_ , _anonymous_ information about our user base and usage patterns.
  * To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences.

**Cookies**

We define a cookie as any string of data that is automatically stored on your computer upon access to our online services. ClickBank employs cookies to assign temporary identification numbers to machines that access our web servers. This information enables us to deliver faster service to our subscribers, prevent denial of service attacks on our systems, detect and prevent fraudulent transactions, and assist with awarding proper sales credit to our partners. All CBGraph cookies are 1) of limited duration, 2) less than 5KB in length, 3) only visible to CBGraph, and 4) devoid of any personally identifiable information.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Security**

We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial or health information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law.

**Policy Modifications**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically.

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [cbgraph@gmail.com](mailto:cbgraph@gmail.com)
